<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Psy.Tests</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="warning_message">Results and interpretations obtained without the participation of specialists should not be taken too seriously.
Only tests conducted by a professional psychologist are of diagnostic value.</string>
    <string name="category_psy">Psychology</string>
    <string name="category_fun">Fun</string>
    <string name="category_relationships">Relationships</string>
    <string name="category_career">Career</string>
    <string name="full_screen_ad_id" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-8407125762950584/1206483423</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="question">Question</string>
    <string name="delete_all_results">Delete all results?</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="warning">Warning</string>
    <string name="low_level">Low level</string>
    <string name="middle_level">Average level</string>
    <string name="high_level">High level</string>
    <string name="save_results">Save tests result</string>
    <string name="version">Version</string>
    <string name="review_app">Rate us</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="result">Result</string>
    <string name="test_description">Test description</string>
    <string name="pass">Start</string>
    <string name="privacy_link">https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Dlt4cGz-V3wP3UXUY0LPwKErWBxuE_xHOBnp5BYQ-Zc</string>
    <string name="no_history">No history yet</string>
    <string name="test_of_day">Recommended</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="my_results">My results</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact us</string>
    <string name="luscher_pause_title">Take a rest for 5 minutes</string>
    <string name="luscher_pause_text">The testing method involves two approaches with a small interval between them. Please wait a few minutes, and then click "continue". Don\'t try to remember the order in which you chose the colors the first time. But do not try to specifically put them in a different way. Just choose your favorite colors as if you are seeing them for the first time</string>
    <string name="continue_text">Continue</string>
    <string name="pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="warning_message_2">We do not give detailed interpretations of the results so that you can discuss your preliminary result with a specialist.</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="szondi_positive_instruction">Choose the two most pleasant or cute portrait. If you don\'t like any of them, then choose the two least unpleasant ones</string>
    <string name="szondi_negative_instruction">Choose two of the most unpleasant, unsympathetic portraits</string>

    <string name="five_scales_low_score">Low score</string>
    <string name="five_scales_below_average">Below average</string>
    <string name="five_scales_average_rates">Average values</string>
    <string name="five_scale_values_above_average">Above average</string>
    <string name="five_scales_high_index">High values</string>

    <string name="luscher_result_4">Perception of arousal to discharge tension. Waiting for meetings, disclosure, fussiness, escape from problems, illusory expectation of the future.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_1">The desire for peace. Intense need for pleasant communication and satisfaction, striving for harmony, sensitivity.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_2">Willpower. Self-assertion, vanity, spontaneous desire to play a certain role.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_3">Striving for emotions. Active participation and high activity.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_5">Readiness for peace without tension, pleasant relationships and satisfaction.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_6">Self-determination, self-control.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_7">Stagnation, annoyance, irritability.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_8">Ready for contacts.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_9">Surface connections and relationships.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_10">Low level of pretension, passive attitude to social order.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_11">Nervous irritability, needs careful handling, lack of desires.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_12">Critical attitude to the choice of contacts and hobbies.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_13">Anxiety, fussiness, lack of deep "heart" connections, dissatisfaction with the relationship with a partner and their activities.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_14">Restriction of self-expression, protective tension, denied recognition. Others are perceived as exerting cruel, heartless pressure, forcing them to do what they do not want.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_15">Overexpression, feeling of weakness, feeling of helplessness. Offended, hardly copes with business. Tired and poorly oriented in the environment.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_16">Restless waiting. Thematic fixation, limitation of self-disclosure. Stiffness, overexcitation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_17">Isolation, cautious restraint, closeness, secrecy, social isolation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_18">The desire to charm, sensuality, suggestibility.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_20">Expression of protest, negativism, impulsive and aggressive behavior.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_19">Regression to physical needs, escape from problems.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_21">Limited emotional readiness for contacts. Disconnection.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_22">Sensuality.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_23">The need for comfort and physical satisfaction.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_24">Protest and withdrawal from a partner or situation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_25">Emotional readiness to communicate. Interest in social relations.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_26">Restrains his feelings. Reflection of feelings. Scrupulousness. Sensitivity and touchiness.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_27">Discharge of physical needs.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_28">The ability to tolerate limitations, to make compromises. Agrees to the terms.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_29">Emotional excitability, striving for social success.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_30">Suppression of sensitivity, control of feelings. Aesthetic, ethical, or logical pursuit of order.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_31">Suppression, displacement or inhibition of physical needs.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_32">Rejection of interference and restrictions, ignoring threats, enterprise.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_33">Feeling of contentment, calmness, desire for a calm environment, unwillingness to participate in conflicts, stress.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_34">A sense of integrity, an active and not always conscious desire for a close relationship. The need for attention from others.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_35">Slight anxiety, the need for a subtle environment, the desire for aesthetic.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_36">Feeling of anxiety, fear of loneliness, desire to get away from conflict, avoid stress.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_37">Negative state, desire for peace, rest, dissatisfaction with self-attitude, negative attitude to the situation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_38">Negative state, the need to get rid of stress, the desire for peace, rest.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_39">Negative state, the need to get rid of stress, the desire for peace, rest.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_40">A positive state, a desire for recognition, for activities that ensure success.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_41">Active pursuit of success, independent decisions, overcoming obstacles in activit.y</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_42">Slight anxiety, desire for recognition, popularity, desire to impress.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_43">Slight anxiety, desire for recognition, popularity, desire for super impressions, increased attention to the reactions of others to their actions.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_44">Feeling of dissatisfaction, fatigue, overestimation of the importance of the attitude towards oneself from others.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_45">Dissatisfaction, desire for recognition, desire to impress.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_46">Feelings of resentment, anger, desire for pity, authoritarianism in relationships.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_47">Feelings of resentment, anger, desire for pity, authoritarianism in relationships.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_48">Business excitement, active pursuit of activities, impressions, pleasures.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_49">Business excitement, active pursuit of goals, overcoming all difficulties, striving for a high evaluation of their activities.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_50">Businesslike, slightly increased excitement, enthusiasm, optimism, desire for contacts, expansion of the field of activity.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_51">Increased excitement, not always adequate enthusiasm, the desire to impress.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_52">Negative mood, frustration due to failure, unwillingness to lose a favorable situation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_53">Negative mood, anger, desire to get out of an unfavorable situation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_54">A feeling of dissatisfaction, a focus on risky action.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_55">A feeling of dissatisfaction, a focus on risky action.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_56">The mood is generally positive, striving for a positive emotional state, mutual support.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_57">The mood is generally positive, the desire to find the first ways to solve the problems, the desire for self-affirmation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_58">Somewhat increased business excitement, the desire for broad activity.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_59">A little euphoria, a desire for bright events, a desire to impress.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_60">Negative mood, frustration and the need for emotional release and rest.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_61">A very negative mood, a desire to get away from any problems, a tendency to necessary, inadequate solutions.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_62">Negative depressed standing, the desire to get out of an unpleasant situation, a clear idea of how to do it.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_63">Somewhat increased business excitement, the desire for broad activity.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_64">Uncertain mood, striving for harmony and harmony.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_65">Alertness, desire to impress.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_66">Some excitement, enthusiasm, an active desire to impress.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_67">Excitement, fantasizing, striving for bright events.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_68">Excitement, focus on strong emotional experiences.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_69">Negative state.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_70">Tension, the desire to protect yourself from conflicts, stress.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_71">Negative state.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_72">Tension, fear of loneliness, desire to get out of an unfavorable situation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_73">Feeling anxious, striving for strict self-control to avoid mistakes.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_74">An active desire for emotional release.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_75">Loss of faith in positive prospects, the likelihood of rash decisions ("I don't care").</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_76">A feeling of dissatisfaction, a desire for comfort.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_77">Negative state, frustration, desire for peace, desire to get away from activity.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_78">A very negative state, a desire to get away from difficult problems rather than fight them.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_79">A feeling of dissatisfaction, a desire for comfort.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_80">A very negative state, the desire to get away from problems ("would be left alone").</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_81">Excitement, angry attitude towards others, not always adequate stubbornness.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_82">Strong arousal, possible affective behavior.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_83">Very negative state, despair, suicidal thoughts.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_84">Tension, dreams of harmony.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_85">Excitement, setting unrealistic tasks, striving to get away from restless thoughts, unfavorable situations.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_86">Feeling hopeless, doomed, striving to resist everything, inadequacy.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_87">Tension, dreams of harmony.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_88">Negative state, desire for a calm situation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_89">Negative state, feeling of hostility of others and the desire to protect yourself from the environment.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_90">Negative state, lofty demands on others, not always adequate activity.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_91">Negative state, the desire to get away from problems rather than solve them.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_92">A feeling of anxiety and alertness, a desire to hide this feeling.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_93">A very negative attitude, the desire to get away from everything complicated, difficult, from excitement.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_94">A very negative state, resentment, a sense of oppression, the likelihood of inadequate decisions.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_95">Negative state, the desire to get away from problems rather than solve them.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_96">Relatively passive, is in a static state. The need for mutual affection is not satisfied.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_97">The situation is difficult, but he is trying hard to achieve his goal despite the resistance.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_98">In the exercise of his motives, he encounters obstacles and difficulties. Due to tension and conflicts, he is touchy, quickly irritated, loses his temper.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_99">Unjustified hopes and inability to determine what measures to take caused significant stress.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_100">Conflicting tension prevents the establishment of complete mutual intimacy.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_101">Due to conflicting tensions, he feels tired and needs rest.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_102">is under stress, i.e. cannot fulfill the requirements imposed on him by the circumstances. He considers himself forced, at least for a while, to abandon his claims in order to avoid further tension.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_103">Due to conflicting tensions, he feels tired and needs rest.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_104">Strives to resolutely defend its claims, despite opposition</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_105">Strives for calm and lasting confidence. Needs respect, recognition and understanding from close people.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_106">Feels that he is being hindered in showing initiative, but firmly adheres to claims, looking for ways and means to implement his intentions.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_107">Closely monitors the events in which it participates. He disagrees and develops his own opinion.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_108">Would like other people to understand his desires and needs and show compliance. He knows how to deftly justify himself.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_109">He is trying to create a solid foundation for a calm, safe, problem-free future in which he will receive respect and recognition.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_110">He defends his claims and demands with uncompromising persistence.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_111">He defends his claims and demands with uncompromising persistence.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_112">Willingness to establish peaceful relations in order to relieve tension. Needs peace, which he can find in the company of a loved one.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_113">Strives to establish a calm and strong relationship in order to feel recognized, valued and loved.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_114">Feels hindrances, obstacles in the realization of his desires. He wants to get rid of the boiling anger, relieve tension and find peace in a heartfelt unity.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_115">Attaches great importance to his heart experiences, so his own well-being depends on the harmony of the relationship.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_116">Is sensitive, needs an equally sensitive and understanding partner. Ready for full mutual understanding and sensitivity of intimacy.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_117">Needs protection and care. Avoids making any excessive efforts. Feels the need for security, calm and friendly communication.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_118">Needs peace and warm companionship, but requires a partner to be considerate and respectful to himself. Tends to stop communicating if he can\'t count on the desired attitude towards himself.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_119">Strives to establish a calm and strong relationship in order to feel recognized, valued and loved.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_120">Gets annoyed quickly due to tension, but tries to avoid conflicts.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_121">Feels that he is prevented from fulfilling his desires, seeks to get rid of accumulated annoyance, relieve tension and find peace in a heart connection.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_122">Shows initiative in overcoming difficulties. Wants to occupy a position in which he would be invested with power and could control the course of events.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_123">Feels that he is being prevented from actively manifesting himself, because his desires remain unfulfilled.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_124">Reacts strongly to stimulating sensory stimuli.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_125">Does not want to expend excessive effort, prefers moderate comfort and safety to those benefits that promise great ambition.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_126">Irritated by inhibition of motivating impulses. He closes in on himself with disgust if his needs remain unsatisfied.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_127">Reacts strongly to stimulating sensory stimuli.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_128">Unsatisfied. Feels the need to eliminate existing conflicts and difficulties. Looking for a way out of this situation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_129">With uncompromising persistence, he demands and achieves the fulfillment of his claims. If his claims are not satisfied, he breaks off the relationship with disgust.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_130">Believes that he is being blocked and prevented from getting what he considers important for himself. He is dissatisfied and breaks off the relationship with disgust.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_131">Abruptly breaks off the relationship if his high hopes are not properly justified.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_132">Strives for a relationship based on sensitivity and mutual understanding. Refuses relationships that do not bring complete refined intimacy.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_133">Physical illness, overexertion have taken a serious form. Very disappointed in the connection and rejects it. Needs care, careful attitude.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_134">Needs the right connection for his own peace of mind. However, it makes high demands on the partner. If the relationship does not meet the required requirements, it abruptly breaks them.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_135">Denial of any limitations of his personality, active pursuit of activity.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_136">Feels tired of conflicts. Needs rest, a sense of security and physical sensual satisfaction.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_137">Strives to establish itself despite existing obstacles. Hardly meets the requirements imposed on him. He perceives difficulties as exhausting and hopes to avoid further troubles, wants the situation to become easier. Needs a sense of security.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_138">I would like to compensate for inhibited impulses with the help of sensual satisfaction. Since further successes are associated with difficulties for him, he strives for a calmer environment in which he would avoid unrest.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_139">Strives for conflict-free satisfaction of his desires and sensual pleasures.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_140">x6 x5 is sensitive. Strives for thrills and sensual pleasure. Rejects everything tasteless, vulgar, rude.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_141">Needs a sense of security and calm friendly communication. May be in poor physical condition and need gentle treatment and attentive help.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_142">Physical illness, overexertion have taken a serious form. Self-esteem has dropped. Needs care, careful attitude, satisfaction of their desires.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_143">Denial of any limitations of his personality, active pursuit of activity.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_144">Attaches great importance to the feelings of the heart. For this reason, one\'s own well-being depends on the harmony of relationships.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_145">Closely monitors events in which he takes part Does not agree with the opinions of others and develops his own opinion.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_146">Since expectations remain unfulfilled, he believes that he is prevented from actively manifesting himself. Because of this, he is irritable and dissatisfied.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_147">Hopes to find a way to get rid of the oppressive tension.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_148">Dreams of an unencumbered, sensually exciting contact.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_149">Strives for conflict-free satisfaction of its needs and sensual enjoyment.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_150">Demands and waits impatiently for the fulfillment of his desires and hopes.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_151">Demands and waits impatiently for the fulfillment of his desires and hopes.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_152">Due to conflict tension, he feels an increased need for sweaty mutual understanding and sensitivity of intimacy.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_153">Behaves tactfully, skillfully, insists on fulfilling his claims, but he is not ready to meet the wishes of others.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_154">Reacts strongly to sensory-stimulating stimuli.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_155">Is looking for a non-burdensome, stimulating contact.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_156">Feels the need for a cordial connection and full mutual understanding and sensitivity of intimacy.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_157">Strives for thrills, sensual satisfaction.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_158">Needs a relationship full of intimacy and understanding. Refuses to connect without full, refined intimacy.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_159">Strives for thrills, sensual satisfaction.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_160">Feeling of dissatisfaction, emotional tension.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_161">Emotional tension, desire to get out of an unfavorable situation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_162">Irritability, feeling of helplessness.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_163">Anxiety, self-doubt.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_164">Small controlled excitation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_165">Anxiety, self-doubt, but at the same time excessive demands, the desire to achieve recognition of his personality.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_166">Denial of any limitations of his personality, active pursuit of activity.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_167">Denial of any limitations of his personality, active pursuit of activity</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_168">Somewhat depressed state, anxiety, feeling of hopelessness.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_169">Strong tension, the desire to get rid of a negative stressful state.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_170">Strong tension, feeling of helplessness, desire to get out of an emotional situation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_171">A state close to stress, emotional negative experiences, a feeling of helplessness.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_172">A state close to stress, the complexity of relationships, a sense of limited possibilities, impatience.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_173">Emotional dissatisfaction, self-restraint, search for support.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_174">A state close to stress, emotional dissatisfaction, the desire to get out of a psychogenic situation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_175">Emotional dissatisfaction, self-restraint, search for support.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_176">Depressed state of disbelief in their own strength, the desire to get out of an unpleasant situation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_177">A state of frustration, irritability due to a number of failures, a decrease in volitional qualities.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_178">Strong excitement, painful experiences, considers relations with the environment hostile, affective actions are possible.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_179">A state close to frustration, a feeling of disappointment, indecision.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_180">A state close to stressful, a sense of offended dignity, disbelief in one\'s own strength.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_181">A state close to stressful, inadequately increased self-control, unreasonable desire for recognition.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_182">State of frustration due to limitations of ambitious requirements, lack of commitment.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_183">A state close to frustration, a feeling of disappointment, indecision.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_184">Suppressed excitement, irritability, impatience, the search for a way out of negative relationships with loved ones.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_185">State of stress due to inadequate self-esteem.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_186">Pent-up excitement, a sense of lost perspective, the likelihood of nervous exhaustion.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_187">Suspiciousness, anxiety, inadequate assessment of the environment, the desire for self-justification.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_188">State of stress due to unsuccessful attempts to reach mutual understanding, feeling of insecurity, helplessness, desire for sympathy.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_189">Strong tension caused sometimes by sexual self-restraint, lack of friendly contacts, lack of self-confidence.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_190">A state of stress due to deep disappointment, frustration, a feeling of anxiety, powerlessness to solve a conflict problem, a desire to get out of a frustrating situation in any way, doubt that it will succeed.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_191">State of stress due to inadequate self-esteem.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_192">A feeling of frustration, a state close to stress, a desire to suppress negative emotions.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_193">State of indecision, anxiety, frustration.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_194">A state of stress accompanied by excitement, doubts about success, claims not supported by real opportunities, self-justification.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_195">Emotional frustration and feelings of anxiety, anxiety, frustration.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_196">Tension, feeling of insecurity, wariness, the desire to avoid control from the outside.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_197">State of indecision, anxiety, frustration.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_198">A feeling of dissatisfaction that stimulates activity, a desire for cooperation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_199">Stressful states due to unfulfilled self-affirmation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_200">Stressful state due to failures in active, sometimes thoughtless actions.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_201">Alertness, suspicion, disappointment, isolation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_202">The manifestation of impatience, but at the same time the desire for self-control, causes some emotional excitement.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_203">Stress caused by the violation of desirable relationships, increased exactingness to others.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_204">Tension due to limitations in independent decisions, the desire for mutual understanding, frank expression of thoughts.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_205">Stressful states due to unfulfilled self-affirmation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_206">A negative state, a feeling of dissatisfaction due to insufficient recognition of merits (real and assumed), a desire for self-restraint and self-control.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_207">A negative state due to excessive self-control, a stubborn desire to stand out, doubts that it will succeed.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_208">A stressful state due to the suppression of erotic and other biological needs, the desire for cooperation to get out of stress.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_209">The intensity of the desire to hide anxiety under the mask of confidence and carelessness.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_210">A negative state due to an unsatisfied desire for sensitive harmony.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_211">Stressful state due to suppression of biological, sexual needs.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_212">Desire to leave subordination, negative attitude to various prohibitions.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_213">The desire to get out of submission, a negative attitude to various prohibitions.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_214">A state of anxiety in connection with a hidden desire to get help, support.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_215">A state close to frustration due to the restriction of freedom of desired actions, the desire to get rid of interference.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_216">Stressful state caused by disappointment in the expected situation, emotional arousal.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_217">Stressful state due to fear of further failures, refusal of reasonable compromises.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_218">The search for an idealized situation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_219">Stressful state due to unpleasant restrictions, prohibitions, the desire to resist restrictions, to escape from mediocrity.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_220">The desire to get out of an unfavorable situation.</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_221">The desire to get out of an unfavorable situation.</string>

    <string name="one_scale_result_1">Absence of depressive symptoms</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_2">Mild depression (subdepression)</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_3">Moderate depression</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_4">Severe depression (moderate severity)</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_5">Severe depression</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_6">Normal state</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_7">Mild depression</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_8">Moderate depression</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_9">Severe depression</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_10">Normal state</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_11">Negative attitude towards the future</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_12">Moderate feeling of hopelessness</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_13">Strong feeling of hopelessness</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_14">Low level of anxiety</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_15">Average anxiety level</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_16">High level of anxiety</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_17">Low level of reflexivity</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_18">Average level of reflexivity development</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_19">High level of reflexivity development</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_20">There is no orthorexia nervosa</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_21">There is a probability of orthorexia nervosa</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_22">Absolutely dysfunctional family</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_23">High degree of dissatisfaction</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_24">Expressed dissatisfaction</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_25">Transitional status</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_26">Marriage satisfaction</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_27">Happy family</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_28">Absolutely prosperous family</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_29">Very low level of empathy</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_30">Low level of empathy</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_31">Average level of empathy</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_32">High level of empathy</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_33">Very high level of empathy</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_34">Low level of approval motivation</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_35">Average expression of approval motivation</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_36">High expression of approval motivation</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_37">Low level of achievement motivation</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_38">Average intensity of achievement motivation</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_39">High degree of achievement motivation</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_40">Low alarm level</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_41">Average alarm level</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_42">High alarm level</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_43">Very high alarm level</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_44">Low neuroticism</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_45">High probability of neurosis</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_46">Regular internet user</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_47">There are some problems associated with excessive internet addiction</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_48">Internet addiction</string>
    <string name="one_scale_result_49">Regular internet user</string>

    <string name="szondi_result_1">The tendency of love for humanity, humanism. Craving for culture, love of nature</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_2">Tenderness, pliability, softness of character</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_3">The trend towards personal love and tenderness</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_4">Civility, passivity, humility, willingness to sacrifice, nobility</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_5">Courage, activity, aggressiveness, sadism, cruelty, enterprise, perseverance</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_6">Accumulation of anger, jealousy, intolerance, hatred, malice, vindictiveness, vindictiveness</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_7">Kindness, justice, tolerance, gentleness, willingness to help another, simplicity, benevolence</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_8">Modesty, moral censorship, tendency to fantasize, shame, deceitfulness, timidity, cowardice</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_9">Demonstrativeness, desire to impress others, artistry, thirst for approval, ambition</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_10">Passion for denial, destruction, selflessness, the desire to adapt to the collective</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_11">Egocentrism, pedantry, resentment, tendency to logically reasonable processes, stubbornness</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_12">Low self-esteem, caution, suspicion, vulnerability, distrust, scrupulousness</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_13">Striving for leadership, rivalry; overestimated self-esteem, fervor, self-evaluation, enthusiasm</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_14">Loyalty, greed, inertia</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_15">Curiosity, uncertainty, impermanence</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_16">Tendencies towards loneliness and independence, fussiness</string>
    <string name="szondi_result_17">Striving for pleasure, fun, presence in a group, impermanence</string>

    <string name="test20_result_1">Unconditional self-confidence, increased self-esteem, independence, stenicity, striving for dominance in social contacts</string>
    <string name="test20_result_2">A high level of self-confidence, self-esteem and the ability to self-actualize, the absence of problems in decision-making, the desire for independence and dominance in social relations, the ability to take responsibility and achieve goals</string>
    <string name="test20_result_3">Currently, the problems associated with self-acceptance and self-satisfaction are not relevant for the individual; one can assume a sufficient degree of confidence in making decisions and making social contacts, a balanced emotional background and pattern of behavior, the adequacy of self-perception (the absence of both an overly critical attitude towards oneself and self-esteem)</string>
    <string name="test20_result_4">The presence in the current mental state and personality structure of traits of anxiety, self-doubt, increased propensity for critical introspection, difficulties in decision-making; one can assume a dependent-compliant position and increased emotional exhaustion in social contacts, the need for emotional support, insufficient independence and stenicity in achieving the goal</string>
    <string name="test20_result_5">High anxiety, uncertainty, difficulties in making decisions and in choice situations, a tendency to carefully consider actions, introspection; dissatisfaction with oneself, low self-esteem; in social relations – timidity, dependence, expectation of failure, failure, rejection; lack of stenicity and independence in behavior</string>
    <string name="test20_result_6">Low intellectual productivity, slowing of associative processes, tendency to long-term thinking; limited range and undifferentiated nature of interests; low social activity, insufficient sociability, difficulties in establishing contacts, absence or reduction of the need for wide and diverse interpersonal relationships</string>
    <string name="test20_result_7">Insufficient productivity (increased exhaustion) and insufficient plasticity (difficulty switching) of intellectual activity, a tendency to reflection and in-depth reflection, insufficient spontaneity in decisions, a narrow range of interests, lack of expression of cognitive need and receptivity to the new; in social contacts – a decrease in initiative and interest, a tendency to distance; in general, a low level of social competence and activity of the individual</string>
    <string name="test20_result_8">Currently, an average level of intellectual productivity and plasticity, a moderate pace of associative reactions, moderate expression of cognitive interests, lack of a pronounced desire to search for various types of information is revealed; social behavior is characterized by a moderate level of activity, sociability, entrepreneurship, involvement in interpersonal interaction and interest in broad contacts </string>
    <string name="test20_result_9">The lowered value of the assessment reflects a definitely high level of intellectual productivity and cognitive interests, receptivity to new things, plasticity, the ability to make quick decisions; in the field of social relations – confidence, good communication skills and organizational abilities, the desire for a variety of contacts and activities, emotional involvement</string>
    <string name="test20_result_10">High mobility and plasticity of intellectual processes, diverse interests, active search for information and impressions; social courage, confidence, perseverance, risk-taking, desire for wide and diverse contacts</string>
    <string name="test20_result_11">Uncertainty in combination with increased introspection, conscious and rigid control of behavior, an exaggerated tendency to ponder actions, planning, rationalization; inertia and "jamming" of experiences; in behavior and social contacts – "tightness", lack of looseness, spontaneity, naturalness and ease</string>
    <string name="test20_result_12">The need for careful planning and deliberation of actions, the desire to complete what has been started, the difficulties of switching from one type of activity to another; accuracy, correctness, pedantry, patience in work and social interaction; at the same time, the motivation of avoiding failure dominates the motivation of high achievements; in general, a serious attitude to life combined with the difficulty of free self-realization</string>
    <string name="test20_result_13">Currently, the problems associated with free self-realization are not relevant for the individual; behavior has a rather spontaneous, relaxed nature, there is no pronounced tendency to increased reflection and critical introspection, careful deliberation and planning of actions; a moderate degree of responsibility, commitment, and plasticity is characteristic (lack of a pronounced tendency to fix experiences, an accepted line of behavior, completion of what has been started)</string>
    <string name="test20_result_14">The absence of problems associated with free self-realization, increased control of behavior and emotional reactions, fixed forms of behavior and experiences; in activities and social relationships – naturalness, ease, lack of inclination to careful planning, deliberation and completion of what has been started, ease of switching from one type of activity and contacts to another, impatience, mobility; motivation of high achievements prevails over the motivation of avoiding failure.</string>
    <string name="test20_result_15">Spontaneity of emotional reactions, looseness of behavior, free self-realization, dynamism of decisions, assessments, actions, lack of introspection and tendency to reflection, self-confidence; easy attitude to problems, failures, responsibility, lack of fear of new activities, contacts, focus on success and high achievements</string>
    <string name="test20_result_16">The high value of the assessment reflects the high probability of unrestrained, poorly controlled and predictable behavior; the predominance of affective forms of reaction (mainly extrapunitive orientation), irritability, quick temper; non-conformity and rashness of actions; poor tolerance of stress with the possibility of maladaptive forms of behavior, aggressiveness; at the same time, there are features of hypersensitivity to injustice, sensitivity and affective rigidity</string>
    <string name="test20_result_17">The increased value of the assessment reflects increased emotional excitability, weakening of the ability to willfully control emotions, unstable, unbalanced behavior in interpersonal interaction, the possibility of irritable and angry reactions in frustrating situations, increased sensitivity with a tendency to "accumulate" negative experiences (insufficient plasticity of emotions); reduced tolerance to stress and, in general, the regulatory capabilities of the psyche </string>
    <string name="test20_result_18">The evaluation value falls into the zone of an uncertain diagnosis. This means that currently there are no significant problems associated with the control of affective reactions; behavior is characterized by sufficient poise, balance (the predominance of extrapunitive reactions is not expressed); one can assume the ability to suppress sensitivity, irritability and other negatively colored emotional reactions and states, a moderate (sufficient) level of tolerance to stress, the ability to use constructive mechanisms of psychological overcoming (coping behavior); in general, the absence of significant difficulties in regulating behavior and social adaptation </string>
    <string name="test20_result_19">The lowered value of the assessment reflects a balanced, stable and predictable pattern of behavior, the adequacy of emotional response methods, good intellectual and volitional control of behavior; there is no pronounced tendency to form "stuck" sensitive reactions (plasticity of emotions); stability in stress, constructive forms of psychological overcoming and adaptation </string>
    <string name="test20_result_20">The low value of the assessment reflects emotional stability and balance, the absence of affective conditioning and rashness of behavior, as well as affective rigidity and sensitivity; high frustration tolerance, the predominance of plastic and constructive ways to overcome stress</string>
    <string name="test20_result_21">The high value of the assessment reflects significant social distancing, immersion in the world of one\'s own experiences, the need for solitude, experiencing discomfort in situations of broad social interaction, an individual pattern of behavior, ways of activity and solving problem situations</string>
    <string name="test20_result_22">The increased value of the assessment reflects social distancing, preference for activities that do not involve broad social interaction, autonomy of behavior (independence from the assessments of others), independence of judgments, the desire to suppress external manifestations of emotions; trusting relationships can develop with a very limited circle of people </string>
    <string name="test20_result_23">The evaluation value falls into the zone of uncertain diagnosis. This means that at present there is a moderate level of social activity, sociability and conformity, the absence of significant difficulties in implementing social contacts, a moderate need for understanding and support from others, the possibility of trusting relationships with a relatively wide range of people and the natural manifestation of emotions in behavior</string>
    <string name="test20_result_24">The lowered value of the assessment reflects rather sociable, open behavior, willingness to cooperate, orientation to the opinions of others, the need for their help and support, open expression of emotions outside and the ability to establish trusting relationships with a fairly wide range of people; plasticity and lack of difficulties in implementing social contacts, establishing new connections</string>
    <string name="test20_result_25">A low score value reflects a distinct socially oriented behavior, openness and ease in contacts, the need for communication, a good ability for group interaction</string>
    <string name="test20_result_26">The high value of the assessment reflects excessive concentration on individual mental and somatic functions, on the state of one\'s health as a whole, the desire to maintain an exclusively correct lifestyle in order to avoid illness, anxiety concerns about the risk of developing the disease</string>
    <string name="test20_result_27">The increased value of the assessment reflects concentration on the state of one\'s health, attentive attitude to minor manifestations of malaise, increased control over behavior and lifestyle in order to avoid situations potentially associated with the risk of disease (hypothermia, overexertion, etc.), search for information about various diseases and compliance with all prescriptions for their prevention; inflexibility of behavior in general, discomfort if necessary, changes in habitual life stereotypes</string>
    <string name="test20_result_28">The evaluation value falls into the zone of an uncertain diagnosis. This means that at present, increased control over the state of one\'s health, individual mental and somatic functions, lifestyle and behavior in connection with the risk of developing diseases is not typical for the subject; there is a moderate degree of plasticity and a reasonable approach to the problem of preserving and maintaining health, to obtaining the necessary information about diseases and measures to prevent them, a balanced nature of experiences related to the state of health in general </string>
    <string name="test20_result_29">The lowered value of the assessment reflects the lack of a tendency to increased control over the state of one\'s health and behavior (lifestyle) that can affect its level, plasticity (lack of fixation on unpleasant sensations, experiences, as well as anxiety in situations requiring changes in behavioral stereotypes), a light (non-anxious) attitude to emerging symptoms of malaise, the possibility of deviation from prescriptions and recommendations for treatment and maintenance of health.</string>
    <string name="test20_result_30">A low score value reflects a careless, non-anxious attitude to one\'s state of health, lack of desire for preventive measures due to the risk of illness and a sparing lifestyle</string>
    <string name="test20_result_31">The high value of the assessment reflects poor adaptability in various social situations, a decrease in social perception and understanding of the nuances of interpersonal relationships, lack of criticality regarding the correctness and acceptance of their behavior by others</string>
    <string name="test20_result_32">The increased value of the assessment reflects a decrease in the level of social adaptability, manifested in insufficient ability to understand the nuances of interpersonal relationships (social perception and empathy), in the inflexibility of social contacts, non-conformity; a reduced level of socialization is also manifested in insufficient experience (dexterity, sophistication) in solving difficult social situations, in insufficient ability to control the clarity and acceptance of one\'s judgments and actions, in the resulting ambivalent attitude towards others (the need for communication is combined with the fear of being awkward, misunderstood); there may be a deviation from generally accepted forms of behavior due to personal unconventionality, unusual attitudes, poor assimilation of social norms</string>
    <string name="test20_result_33">The evaluation value falls into the zone of uncertain diagnosis. This means that there are currently no pronounced signs of violations of social adaptation due to insufficient assimilation of generally accepted norms, a decrease in social perception, empathy, communication skills, flexibility and confidence in the process of interpersonal interaction</string>
    <string name="test20_result_34">The lowered value of the assessment reflects a well-balanced social behavior based on the correct assimilation of generally accepted patterns of behavior, on general good communication skills, a high level of socio- and autoperception in the process of interpersonal interaction, plasticity, compliance and interest in social contacts</string>
    <string name="test20_result_35">The low value of the assessment reflects significant adaptive capabilities of the individual, plasticity, differentiation of social behavior; good communication skills and a desire for cooperation</string>

    <string name="test22_result_1">Does not remember any insults, is not vindictive, does not notice insults, lacks ambition, does not pay any attention to critical remarks. There are no egocentric impulses (or they are blocked). The boundaries of the mental image of the "I" are not delineated, the attitude towards oneself is not developed. Formation of motivation is difficult.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_2">Does not remember insults for long, revenge passes quickly, insults are quickly forgotten, adequate ambition, adequately respond to critical remarks.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_3">He does not remember insults for long, revenge passes quickly, insults are quickly forgotten, adequate ambition, adequately respond to critical remarks.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_4">Denies the desire for thoroughness, accuracy, self-control. At home and at work, he is a complete mess. Permissiveness, impunity, irresponsibility are manifestations at the everyday level. This feature can be both the result of social neglect and a form of psychological protection.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_5">He is careful in moderation: at home and at work he tries to maintain order as needed; he does not like, but agrees to do work that requires thoroughness.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_6">Is careful in moderation: at home and at work, he tries to maintain order as needed; does not like, but agrees to do work that requires thoroughness.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_7">Is characterized by shyness, developed ethical complex, sincerity and depth of feelings. An anxious, passive person, prefers to stay "in the shadows", avoids large crowds of people.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_8">Average sociability; avoids exposing himself, but also does not hide from people if you need to speak in front of a large audience.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_9">Average sociability; avoids exposing himself, but also does not hide from people if you need to speak in front of a large audience.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_10">Shows exceptional composure, a high level of self-control and self-regulation in the field of emotional reactions and relationships.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_11">Tries to keep cool, but sometimes loses his temper; is able to adequately control strong desires.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_12">Tries to keep cool, but sometimes loses his temper; is able to adequately control strong desires.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_13">The mood is lowered. Pessimistic. It is uninitiative. Facial expressions are not pronounced, coordination of movements is weak. Does not like fast physical exercises. Low thirst for intellectual activity. Little sociable. A hypochondriac person, a tendency to dependent behavior is possible.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_14">The mood is average. Not pessimistic, not optimistic. Average degree of initiative. Facial expressions are expressed moderately, average coordination of movements. The average need for intellectual activity. Average sociability.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_15">Average mood. Not pessimistic, not optimistic. Average degree of initiative. Facial expressions are expressed moderately, average coordination of movements. The average need for intellectual activity. Average sociability.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_16">Denies (or blocks) shyness, lack of initiative. Its distinctive features are verbosity, emotional mobility, constant involvement in activities, a wide range of behavioral programs.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_17">Moderately talkative, a reasonable pessimist, the mood is even.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_18">Moderately talkative, a reasonable pessimist, the mood is even.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_19">Such a person denies (or blocks) the manifestations of mood swings, changes in activity, describes his behavior as stable, stable, independent of external circumstances</string>
    <string name="test22_result_20">The mood is generally stable.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_21">The mood is generally stable.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_22">Emotional depression is observed. In extreme severity - coldness, "emotional stupidity". All types of activities are not emotionally colored, stereotyped. The impression of emotional alienation is created.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_23">Average emotional sensitivity, stable even mood.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_24">Such a person practically does not cry, shows rudeness and insensitivity towards other people. Denies (or blocks) a feeling of compassion, prone to deviant, to an extreme degree of severity – antisocial behavior</string>
    <string name="test22_result_25">Cries rarely, does not express special feelings for people, shows compassion only if necessary.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_26">Rarely cries, does not express special feelings for people, shows compassion only if necessary.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_27">Denies (or blocks) subjective experiences of fear. Does not feel helplessness, a determined, initiative person, always feels safe. Shows courage in any unknown situation, is not afraid of accidents</string>
    <string name="test22_result_28">The feeling of fear is adequate to the situation.</string>
    <string name="test22_result_29">The feeling of fear is adequate to the situation.</string>

    <string name="three_scales_result_1">Extraversion</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_2">Neuroticism</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_3">False</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_4">Deep introvert</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_5">Introvert</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_6">Ambivalence, uncertainty</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_7">Extrovert</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_8">Bright extrovert</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_9">Low level</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_10">Middle level</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_11">High level</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_12">Very high level</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_13">Norm</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_14">Insincerity in responses</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_15">Emotional exhaustion</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_16">Depersonalization</string>
    <string name="three_scales_result_17">Professional reduction</string>

    <string name="bass_result_1">Physical aggression</string>
    <string name="bass_result_2">Indirect aggression</string>
    <string name="bass_result_3">Annoyance</string>
    <string name="bass_result_4">Negativism</string>
    <string name="bass_result_5">Offense</string>
    <string name="bass_result_6">Suspicion</string>
    <string name="bass_result_7">Verbal aggression</string>
    <string name="bass_result_8">Guilt</string>
    <string name="bass_result_9">Aggressiveness index</string>
    <string name="bass_result_10">Aggressiveness index</string>
    <string name="luscher_intro">Which of these eight colors do you think is the cutest?</string>

    <string name="completed_tests">Completed tests</string>
    <string name="tests">Tests</string>

    <string name="five_scales_result_1">Hardness, hardness</string>
    <string name="five_scales_result_2">Self-reliance</string>
    <string name="five_scales_result_3">Focus on achievements and high status</string>
    <string name="five_scales_result_4">Homophobia</string>
    <string name="five_scales_result_5">Acceptance of impersonal sexuality</string>
    <string name="five_scales_result_6">Acceptance of impersonal sexuality</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_summary_1">Desired goals, or behavior dictated by desired goals</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_summary_2">Rejected or suppressed behaviors, or sources of concern</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_summary_3">Personality traits</string>
    <string name="luscher_result_summary_4">The current state of things and the behavior appropriate for this state of things</string>
    <string name="maslach_result_summary_1">Emotional exhaustion</string>
    <string name="maslach_result_summary_2">Depersonalization</string>
    <string name="maslach_result_summary_3">Reduction of professionalism</string>
    <string name="ost_result_summary_1">Temperament type</string>
    <string name="ost_result_summary_2">Social ergicity</string>
    <string name="ost_result_summary_3">Plasticity</string>
    <string name="ost_result_summary_4">Social plasticity</string>
    <string name="ost_result_summary_5">Tempo or Speed</string>
    <string name="ost_result_summary_6">Social tempo</string>
    <string name="ost_result_summary_7">Emotionality</string>
    <string name="ost_result_summary_8">Social emotionality</string>
    <string name="ost_result_summary_9">Control scale</string>

    <string name="sondy_result_factor_1">Factor h</string>
    <string name="sondy_result_factor_2">Factor s</string>
    <string name="sondy_result_factor_3">Factor e</string>
    <string name="sondy_result_factor_4">Factor hy</string>
    <string name="sondy_result_factor_5">Factor k</string>
    <string name="sondy_result_factor_6">Factor p</string>
    <string name="sondy_result_factor_7">Factor d</string>
    <string name="sondy_result_factor_8">Factor m</string>

    <string name="test20_result_summary_1">Self-doubt</string>
    <string name="test20_result_summary_2">Cognitive and social passivity</string>
    <string name="test20_result_summary_3">Neurotic behavior overcontrol</string>
    <string name="test20_result_summary_4">Affective instability</string>
    <string name="test20_result_summary_5">Introverted personality orientation</string>
    <string name="test20_result_summary_6">Hypochondriacal</string>
    <string name="test20_result_summary_7">Social maladaptivity</string>
    <string name="test20_result_summary_8">Simulation</string>
    <string name="test20_result_summary_9">Dissimulation</string>
    <string name="test22_result_summary_1">Stuck</string>
    <string name="test22_result_summary_2">Demonstrativeness</string>
    <string name="test22_result_summary_3">Pedantry</string>
    <string name="test22_result_summary_4">Excitability</string>
    <string name="test22_result_summary_5">Hypertimality</string>
    <string name="test22_result_summary_6">Dysthymicity</string>
    <string name="test22_result_summary_7">Cyclothymicity</string>
    <string name="test22_result_summary_8">Exaltation</string>
    <string name="test22_result_summary_9">Emotivity</string>
    <string name="test22_result_summary_10">Anxiety</string>

    <string name="ost_result_1">Sanguine</string>
    <string name="ost_result_2">Choleric</string>
    <string name="ost_result_3">Phlegmatic</string>
    <string name="ost_result_4">Melancholic</string>
    <string name="ost_result_5">Mixed type</string>
    <string name="ost_result_summary_10">Subject ergicity</string>
    <string name="new_tests">New</string>
    <string name="luscher_test">Luscher test</string>
    <string name="szondi_test">Szondi test</string>
    <string name="ost_result_6">Average value</string>
    <string name="ost_result_7">Low values (3 and 4 points) mean passivity, low level of tone and activation, unwillingness of mental stress, low involvement in the activity process</string>
    <string name="ost_result_8">High values on this scale mean a high need for mastering the subject world, a thirst for activity, a desire for intense mental and physical labor, and ease of mental awakening</string>
    <string name="ost_result_9">Low values - insignificant need for social contacts, withdrawal from socially active forms of behavior, isolation, social passivity</string>
    <string name="ost_result_10">High values - communicative ergicity, the need for social contact, the thirst for mastering social forms of activity, the desire for leadership, sociability, the desire for a high-ranking occupation, mastering the world through communication</string>
    <string name="ost_result_11">Low values - tendency to monotonous work, fear and avoidance of various forms of behavior, viscosity, conservative forms of activity</string>
    <string name="ost_result_12">High values - the ease of switching from one type of activity to another, the rapid transition from one form of thinking to another in the process of interacting with the subject environment, the desire for a variety of forms of subject activity</string>
    <string name="ost_result_13">Low values - difficulty in selecting forms of social interaction, low level of readiness to enter into social contacts, the desire to maintain monotonous contacts</string>
    <string name="ost_result_14">High values - a wide range of communication programs, automatic inclusion in social connections, ease of entering into social contacts, ease of switching in the process of communication, the presence of a large number of communicative blanks, communicative impulsivity</string>
    <string name="ost_result_15">Low values - slowness of actions, low speed of motor-motor operations</string>
    <string name="ost_result_16">High values - high rate of behavior, high speed of operations in the implementation of subject activities, motor-motor speed, high mental speed in the performance of specific tasks</string>
    <string name="ost_result_17">Low values - poorly developed speech motor system, speech slowness, slow verbalization</string>
    <string name="ost_result_18">High values - speech motor speed, speaking speed, high speeds and capabilities of the speech motor apparatus</string>
    <string name="ost_result_19">Low values - insignificant emotional reaction in case of failures, insensitivity to the failure of the case, calmness, self-confidence</string>
    <string name="ost_result_20">High values - high sensitivity to the discrepancy between the planned and expected, planned and the results of a real action, feelings of insecurity, anxiety, inferiority, high anxiety about work, sensitivity to failures, to the discrepancy between the planned, expected, planned and the results of a real action</string>
    <string name="ost_result_21">Low emotionality in the communicative sphere, insensitivity to the assessments of friends, lack of sensitivity to failures in communication, self-confidence and communication situations</string>
    <string name="ost_result_22">High values - high emotionality in the communicative sphere, high sensitivity to failures in communication</string>
    <string name="ost_result_23">Low values - adequate perception of their behavior</string>
    <string name="ost_result_24">High values - an inadequate assessment of their behavior, a desire to look better than they really are</string>


</resources>
